If you still work at the CIA today,
and you got the call from the director
of CIA,
and they said, "You know, John,
I want you to go find out, because
there's so much noise right now in the
marketplace, I want you to go find out
who is actually taking money from
Israel, who's taking money from Cutter,
Qatar, who's taking money from these
different organizations,
whether they are trying to get people to
give pro-Zionist
messaging or trying to give pro-Islam,
you know, it's Sharia's not that bad,
everything's okay, or socialism. How
quickly would you be able to find that
if someone's getting funded or not?
>> I I I get that it's a hypothetical
question. It's an FBI issue. The CIA, by
law, would be forbidden from doing that
on Americans. But, but you could
certainly look at at foreign nationals.
CIA could look at foreign nationals.
You probably need a couple of months to
really dig it up, but you could dig it
up.
>> Would you be able to find out for a fact
like if if
>> Not all of it.
>> So, the reason why I'm asking is cuz I
had the Dominik Tarczyński here. He's a
EU part member of the parliament, and he
tells the story of in 2022, these
multiple EU parliament members
were caught getting uh
>> Ah.
>> uh uh what do you call it?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> big
>> satchel double bag
>> duffel bags
>> That's true.
>> One and a half million dollars.
>> One of them was Greek, and she she's in
prison now. Yes.
>> Yeah, one and a half million dollars of
cash. Can you go to that one, Rob, where
it's Which one is this one? Is this the
one?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, so
one and a half million dollars, but go
to If you can go to the picture Yeah,
that's the lady right there. Whatever
her name is. She was part of the
corruption, and apparently there was so
much money in one of the duffel bags
that they dropped $60,000, 60,000 euros
that they caught afterwards, where cash
was being given. And then, when you go
even deeper, you find that the history
of, you know, nowadays, you know,
King Charles is very pro-Islamist,
you know, pro-It's not It's nothing
wrong with that. Everything is fine. And
then there were reports about him taking
3.2 million dollars. I don't know if
you've seen that report.
>> Like he needs the money.
>> Like he needs the money, but he took 3.2
million dollars.
>> You know, I hate to say it, Pat.
>> Right there. Okay, look at this. From
between 2011 and 2015, then Prince
Charles received approximately 3.2
million dollars in cash payments from
Qatari Prime Minister. This has been
confirmed and he said he did. But he
said the moment money went into their
account, we just gave it to charity
immediately. There was no illegal things
done. You know, we're supposed to
believe that. So, I wondered uh you
know, buying influence. If if the
government all of a sudden I don't even
know if they would pursue this because
because, you know, they may not even
want that man. I If somebody was to come
out like let's just say they did this
with SPLC.
>> Yeah.
>> And all of a sudden they come out and
say, "Let me tell you guys that these
top 50 influencers, who's funding them,
who they're getting money from?" It
would silence the entire market and it
would the fog of war in mainstream media
and podcast and today would be gone.
Everybody would say, "Okay, we know why
you say what you say. We know where your
position is. Great. Can we all move on?
Let's move forward."
>> See, and this is this is exactly why we
need robust oversight, rather than the
cheerleaders on Capitol Hill that we
have. We need people who are really
going to provide independent oversight.
Let me tell you a story and forgive me
that I have to sort of fudge the
language a little bit, but I need to
I had a conversation with a senator
couple of days ago.
Um he
had somebody reach out, "Can you come up
to the office?" I said, "Of course." I
go up there.
And he's concerned about
some documents. He needed to see some
documents. Documents that were
classified in the 1970s.
>> Mhm.
>> I said, "Well, they they should have
been subject to mandatory
declassification. We have a mandatory
declassification law in this country.
After 30 or 35 years, they have to be
declassified unless they contain the
names of a source or um the methods of
an ongoing operation."
And he said, "Exactly."
And they've never been declassified. And
he said, "I went to the CIA and they
said, we don't know what you're talking
about. They're not our documents.
And it turns out that they're Senate
documents. Well, the Senate is not
subject the Congress is not subject to
the Freedom of Information Act. And it's
not subject They always exempt
themselves from their own laws, right?
So, no laws apply on Capitol Hill. They
do anything they want.
And so, I said, uh
well, why don't you go to the
leadership? And he said, I went to
leadership. And they said, they don't
want to get involved in this fight
between two committee chairmen. And I
said, and the other chairman? He said,
the other chairman told me go screw
myself.
And I said, are you kidding me? And he
said, no. He said, I don't know what to
do.
And we sat there for two hours and we
could not come up with a plan.
And it's because there is no oversight.
It's funny to me. You read the
Constitution. The Constitution says that
that the government is made up of three
co-equal branches, the executive, the
legislative, and the judicial.
But that's just not how we treat it. The
the the the legislative has ceded its
authority to the executive. And so, now,
if
you know, there's a Republican in the
White House, Republicans on Capitol Hill
are going to do everything they can to
support their the president and to pass
the president's legislation. The
Democrats have somebody in the White
House, the Democrats in Congress are
going to do everything they can to
support the president. That's not what
the Founding Fathers envisioned. Three
co-equal branches.
And then, what we end [clears throat] up
with is these so-called oversight
committees
that don't oversee anything.
They just egg them on.
>> Yeah, it is so I think I think the the
part with America that
when when I hear people that are tired
like, what are you tired with? What are
you most upset with? I just don't think
there's any accountability.
>> That's exactly what the problem is.
Yeah, I just don't think there's any
accountability. What do you mean? It
seems like they're all in the same
party.
Seems like they all protect you. You
hear that message, right? You can't have
that because that's not good in a
democracy. If there's accountability for
the average person that does something
and then there isn't for the other guys,
what are you talking about? Yeah, I know
there's not. So, I I
I think this administration
uh a story came out. I don't know if you
saw the story came out yesterday saying
that uh again, it's a leak that they
want Tulsi to resign after midterms.
Okay? So, they want Tulsi to resign
after midterms. All right, that story
was leaked. I don't know if it's even a
story there or not. I did There you go,
yeah. Director of Donald Trump
reportedly wants the director national
Okay, who knows what these stories are.
Like we asked you earlier, what stories
do they leak? What do they not? And you
kind of test the market. Who knows what
this is? You know,
on on how they're dropping a story. But
to me, if there's anything this
administration has a shot
at increasing the score the people have
in the CIA, in the FBI, in the US
government a little bit more. Cuz the
way it dropped after Kennedy is a
>> Oh my god.
>> It's like a massive from 72% trust in
the FBI. Can you pull up the history of
trust in the US government or trust in
the FBI or trust in the CIA?
>> And then Watergate?
>> And then Watergate, you know, one by one
by one. Um
there's a chart, Rob. If you go back and
just go to images, you'll see it.
Yeah, it's one of those
that shows the high was 72% and I don't
know what Yeah, zoom in a little bit if
you could. Oh, it doesn't go all the way
back.
It doesn't go all the way back. So, you
you That goes from 97. The one I'm
looking at is from the '60s.
You know, uh
go on the second one. See what the same
the Pew Research. There you go. That's
the one from '58.
>> Wow.
>> Look at that. We used to trust 72%.
>> Look at that.
>> We used to trust the government. We're
like, yeah, they're good, you know,
they're And then we're now in the '20s
and the teens. And that's 15. I would
assume it's even lower today.
>> Like even 9/11, it was barely 50%.
>> Yep. Yep. That's right. Even 9/11 was
50%. At least we're like, "Look,
>> Wow.
>> they're the good people. They're here to
protect us."
>> Yeah.
>> There is a massive mass And by the way,
I think long term, the lower that score
goes,
you you you you cannot risk not knowing
the consequences of the score getting
too low.
>> That's right.
>> Cuz if it gets too low, then what does
the youth do who don't have anything to
lose? Anything. The youth is willing to
break the whole thing cuz they're like,
"You know what? You guys are not doing
anything. You guys are all protecting
each other. You guys are
>> Wow.
>> And then you're dealing with a bigger
problem. So, I hope
they do something to regain the faith.
>> Hi, everybody. I'm John Kiriakou, former
CIA officer. Please find me on Minnect.
We have a lot to talk about. CIA, FBI,
DOD, torture, secret prisons,
international renditions. Maybe you or
your child want to apply for a job at
the CIA and are looking for some tips.
Let me know. There's a lot we can talk
about. You pick the subject, we'll make
it happen. Again, it's on Minnect.
Thanks, and I'll see
>> If you enjoyed this video, you want to
watch more videos like this, click here.
And if you want to watch the entire
podcast, click here.